Smile
Raid on Stohess District (1)
Looking good, Annie!
That's my girl!
What are you doing, Annie?
No breaks!
Wall Sina
Eastern Walled City
What? You hadn't heard?
That Titan kid and the main leadership
Stohess District
have been summoned to the capital.
They'll be coming through town today.
I see.
Then I'm sure he'll end up dissected this time.
Either way, I hope things work out,
and that they seal the gate.
Did you say seal the gate?
You still insist on defiling
the gods with human hands?
Maria! Rose! Sina!
Defiling the three goddesses with
human hands is unforgivable!
Those people love the walls,
and worship them as gods.
Stay away from them.
Ah...
I didn't realize any of them were still around.
Damn it.
Only the walls will protect us!
Military Police
Stohess HQ
You finally woke up.
You look so scary when you sleep,
I couldn't wake you.
Sorry, Annie.
Lately, you've been too lax.
What?
Are you mad?
Well, aren't you a friendly one?
Leave her alone.
Annie's from Trost District.
And she's the only one in this
HQ who's been in a fight.
She just came back from hell.
It'll take her a while to recover.
I get it... You like her.
What's so great about her?
Hitch,
there's only one way a moron like you
makes it into the Military Police.
What's that? I wouldn't know.
Tell me.
Stop it, you two!
Don't bother.
Today, we have a different task for
you than the normal busywork.
That's why I had all of you come here.
It's about the Survey Corps group
that's being summoned to the capital.
They'll be passing through the
city's main street today.
Escorting them is a Military Police HQ job,
so we just need to handle them
as they come through town.
Temporary permission for in-city use of
3D Maneuver Gear has been granted.
You will guard them in tandem
with their own security.
You'll travel by barge to the area
where your mission will begin.
That is all.
May I ask something?
Hmm? What?
What are we protecting them from?
I've never heard of anyone within the
walls acting against the monarchy.
There are minor criminals.
But it's hard to imagine any real organization
unless they were based outside the walls.
And I can't imagine any possible motive.
You're so serious.
Okay, you're in charge of everything.
Here are the details.
We ranking officers are busy.
You guys, handle this on your own.
But don't screw up.
Sorry I held up your game.
Let's get back to it.
Whose turn was it?
Damn! He's just screwing around!
Yeah...
This organization is even more
rotten than I'd imagined.
But of course, that's why I chose it...
But when you're a rookie, they make
you do almost everything.
I didn't know that before.
Scum.
Damn scum who can only
think of themselves!
What are you talking about, Marlow?
Since you chose the MPs, you're no better.
I am better!
I'm not trash like you.
I came here to correct the Military Police.
Wow, Marlow.
I had no idea you were this way.
And how will you do that?
I'll have to work my way up.
When I'm in charge,
I'll fix the discipline issues,
and punish those who are corrupt.
It's simple.
I'll make MP a place for
normal human beings again.
That's all.
The way humans are supposed to be.
Wow, you're the real deal!
And here, I thought you were boring! Sorry!
That's quite a noble goal you've got there.
Good luck.
I'm not so sure.
Huh?
If a "good person" like you ends up in control,
I think that'd be the end for us.
What's this?
You actually have something to say?
I think you're right.
Because you say the right things.
I know someone like that.
Going against the flow takes a lot of courage.
I respect that.
You may just be an idiot, but...
Maybe it's just that the other
guy you know is an idiot.
But I'm not like him.
We've wasted too much time on idle chitchat.
Let's go!
The escort wagons will pass through
the outer gate in forty-five minutes.
When we reach the staging area,
everyone should confirm positions.
Got it?
Uh-huh.
Hey!
What's that?
That's our equipment.
Aren't they taking it deeper within the walls?
But that doesn't explain the
Merchant Association's involvement.
What's going on?
They're selling our equipment
on the black market?
Hey, what about the mission?
Oh, crap... He really is the real deal!
Well, for better or worse, we have time.
Let's enjoy the show.
Okay, let's go get a drink.
What's going on, rookie?
What do you want?
S-Selling government equipment is a crime...
And?
The people's taxes paid
for that equipment, and...
So you're threatening your superiors, rookie?
I'm looking forward to your future.
Go buy yourself a woman, and relax a little.
W-Wait!
Selling government equipment—
H-Hey...
We'll arrest you for opposing a superior officer.
Shut up...
That's illegal...
And no one will care.
Not here!
Could you let him go with that?
I'm sorry... It seems our idiot
is causing problems for you.
We'll teach him a harsh lesson.
Or...
Would you prefer to make a bigger scene?
This is the last time.
Yes, sir!
All right, let's get that drink.
Yeah, it's been a hard day's work.
So do it.
Aren't you going to punish the corrupt?
If you want, I'll help you.
What do you want to eat?
What else?
Meat!
Damn it!
We know you're doing your best, missy.
That isn't true at all...
That idiot you know...
The one you talked about...
Would he have done it?
Maybe.
Then I'm one of those pieces of
trash you were talking about,
the ones who just go with the flow, right?
I don't know.
But isn't that what normal
human beings do, too?
I just want
the weak who do get swept
along with the flow
to be considered human, too.
Annie...
Hey.
You're one of the Military
Police now, aren't you?
Armin...
Information We Can Share So Far:
The Military Police (1)
The Military Police number around 2,000,
but if you add the Garrison under their command,
their actual force is approximately 5,000.
Information We Can Share So Far:
The Military Police (2)
Each walled city has about 200 MP stationed there.
Primary duties are to oversee trainee brigades, monitor
the Garrison, and direct fire-fighting operations.
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm a pack bearer.
I have my Maneuver Gear
hidden under my rain coat.
Look.
What's going on?
Annie, would you assist me
in helping Eren escape?
Escape where?
If you disobey the monarchy,
where will you go inside these walls?
We'll just hide for a while.
I don't intend to fight the monarchy head-on.
It will be reported as a rebellion by
a portion of the Survey Corps.
It'll buy time.
Time we'll spend finding enough ammunition
to counter the other factions at the tribunal.
And we will find it.
Enough ammunition?
Is something so convenient just lying around?
What's your evidence?
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
Sorry, but I can't help you.
I won't tell anyone, but you'll
have to do it on your own.
Annie!
Please!
Eren will be killed!
Clueless people who only care
about saving their own skin
will unwittingly set humanity on
a path toward self-destruction!
I know I can't convince you.
But even so...
I have to make a big wager!
Of course, I'll do my best to
avoid causing you trouble.
But to get through the
checkpoints within Wall Sina,
I need Military Police help!
This is the only way!
Armin...
Do I really look like such
a good person to you?
A good person?
Well...
I don't really like that term.
Because to me,
it just seems to mean someone
who's good for you.
And I don't think there's any one
person who's good for everyone.
So if you don't help me...
Then, to me, you're a bad person, right?
Fine.
I'm in.
That was easier than I thought it'd be.
Shh!
That's the Military Police for you.
You can see how hard they work every day.
Stop staring.
Let's just hope they won't find out
that Jean's taken my place.
That won't last long, though...
We don't look alike at all.
It's fine.
Both of you look like criminals,
with the same nasty look in your eyes.
I don't have a horse face like him.
Hey, if I hadn't helped you, how did
you plan to get over the wall?
I was going to use the Maneuver
Gear to get through.
That's insane.
Wouldn't it have been easier to escape
before you'd reached Stohess?
Why here? And why now?
I felt that the complicated
layout of this city
would give us a better chance
at swapping Eren with Jean.
And I thought pretending to go along with it,
rather than an outright opposition,
would prevent suspicion
and buy our escape more time.
I see.
I get it now.
There!
Here?
Yeah, we go through here.
The remains of an underground city
they planned and abandoned
are still down here.
This takes us
close to the outer gate.
Really? Wow!
Annie?
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you're afraid
of dark, cramped places.
Yes, I am.
I'm sure that a brave,
suicidal bastard like you
wouldn't understand how
a weak girl like me feels.
A girl who can spin a man around
in mid-air isn't weak.
Stop being an idiot. Hurry up!
No, I won't go that way.
It scares me.
If we aren't going above ground, I won't help.
What are you saying?!
Get down here!
Stop screwing around!
Eren, don't shout.
It's not a problem, is it, Mikasa?
For some reason,
there hasn't been anyone nearby for a while.
Jeez!
I'm hurt.
When did you start looking at me that way...
Armin?
Annie, why?
Why did you have Marco's Maneuver Gear?
I remember even its tiniest marks and dings...
because we'd repaired them together.
That's why I recognized them.
I see...
Well... I happened to find it.
Then you killed the two Titans we captured?
Who knows...
But if you thought that a month
ago, why didn't you act then?
Because I still can't believe it!
I wanted to think that my
eyes had deceived me.
And because of that...
But... What about you?
You didn't kill me back then.
And that's why this is happening now.
Yeah, I think so, too.
I never expected you to push me this far.
Why didn't I kill you then?
Hey, Annie...
There's still a chance you're an idiot
who's just going along with this because
you have a shitty sense of humor.
So get down here now!
You can prove something
just by going underground!
Get down here, and prove it!
I can't...
I have failed to become a warrior.
I said this isn't funny!
Let's talk, Annie!
We can still talk—
That's enough.
I can't listen to any more of this.
It's pointless.
I'll tear you apart again, Female Titan!
Armin, I'm glad I could be
a good person to you.
You've won your bet.
But...
This is where my bet begins!
Eren!
Mikasa!
We were too late!
Annie Leonhart was the Female Titan.
However, Eren is unable to transform
before the Female Titan.
It is because the Female Titan is Annie.
Mercy
Raid on Stohess District (2)